That I
Hello Hi Friends My name is Deepak Jain
and I am Powder Infinity Cancel p.m.
How to print Today we will talk about
a health insurance plan of a leading health insurance company. The
name of the product is Repair Shop
Product. If I talk about it, then this product was
launched in 2000 and since then
this product is in great demand in the market.
Before talking about the product, let us talk
about the company. The
company was launched in 2018 as a
joint venture between Max India Limited and Bhopal Group for
International.
After that, these people improved
their working style.
From 2000 till now, they have served three million
plus
customers.
Now, in 2019, Max India Limited
decided to
withdraw the group and they announced their stay quit from now.
After which, the company has been rebranded
and on
10th 2021, the name of the company was changed to Lemon Paa
Health Insurance Company. And if we talk about the
management of this standalone health insurance company, then the
MD and CEO of the company is Mr. Krishnan Ramachandra.
About Krishna Ramachandran Sir  If I am talking about the
health insurance industry,
if I know it from the very beginning or it is
a pattern in the health insurance industry
and he has given many such innovations
to the health insurance industry, in
which we may talk about No Room Rent
Typing or now we will talk about Hari Story
Feel or which we will talk about next Real Shore,
many such new innovations have been given by Krishna
Ramcharan Sharma to the health insurance
industry and if we talk about overall sir's team
also, then if we talk about a very
export health insurance
industry, then next we
talk about green chillies and the product,
as you can see
we have a single introduction of Jhalaria and the
product, so we directly
go on about the benefits and
we discuss the basic USP of the product, the
first dream comes,
if we talk about stomach squeeze for 100 minutes, then the
options are 3 lakh, 4 lakh, 5 lakh, 7.5 lakh, 10.5 lakh, 12.5 lakh,
15 lakh,
20.575 lakh and this means from three lakh to
close to 1 crore  The cover options
available are
always that the minimum cover should be
in any state of India, minimum
cover of ₹10, there is a reason that if
you cover less then you will also
get it on the side as you move forward, it becomes
more and more, one day we talk about
benefits cover up to cover,
it means that if
someone has taken a policy of Rs 10 lakh then cover up to
₹10, the
things that are covered under this cover, the first
point is in-patient care, this time
without any room rent capping, this means that in-
patient care means 24-hour
hospitalization in any health insurance
policy in India, this is mandatory, let's say,
no room rent capping,
this means that you
can take any room of any category, whatever you want, let's
talk about treatment,
see, treatment means that
today medical technology has become very advanced due to
which boxer  Treatment is such
that there is no need to stay in the hospital for 24 hours
and
[music]
Lemon says that if there is any such
treatment which
requires staying in the hospital for even 2 hours, then such
treatment is also covered. Apart from this,
this is called alternative treatments,
which we cover in modern art treatment.
Apart from this, home care
treatment, two mister hospitalization is that treatment
where there is
such a condition somewhere else, in which there is no
hospital near you,
as you must have seen earlier, during the
event, there were no patients in it, so
in such a condition, if the patient stays at home
and gets treatment, then that is also
covered. Living organ donor
transplant is covered. Apart from this, now let's
talk about print hospitalization, which is
60.18, its meaning is that on the
day of admission, you can see 6 bed expenses before admission
and
180 days after discharge are covered in this policy from a span of 180 days. Let's
talk about rear benefit
and  I try to explain the benefit with a very simple example.
Support it
is a glass of water. As soon as the glass of water reduces to
half or less, that glass of water will be
refilled again. Support it.
If someone took a policy of ₹10
and he got admitted in the hospital and
he took the next one for Rs.5 and if
he had to get admitted again for the same amount in the same year, then he
can buy the policy of ₹10 again and back
to back without any additional cost, that is,
without any additional charge. If I talk about booster benefit, then
I personally
like this benefit very much. I will explain it with a very
simple example.
Suppose someone took a policy of Rs.10 lakh and
his policy ran for one year and there was
no claim, then next year his policy would become 10
lakh to 15 lakh. He will get no
claim bonus the next day for the second year and
again his policy ran for the next day and if there was
no claim, then the policy would be up to 10 lakh.  It will become 10
lakhs and there is no need to depend on any additional charge for this, that is,
in 2 years the sum assured will reach 10
lakhs, that is, 20 lakh rupees.
Now let's talk about the very good benefits
given here. There is a mentality in our Indian population
that we
still do not avail the maximum benefit.
As you pay its premium, you are eligible to
avail the benefits from the chapter.
Take the health benefits
subscription benefit and you can download this JP Nibha on
your mobile
and if you run and
work, then you will get premium discount
from the teams till the time of removal of your policy. Let's
talk about modern treatment.
In modern treatment, we talk about robotic
surgery or many such treatments
like support, which are being done in India
and outside, you are
using only USA doctors, so this
entire surgery is
done by robotic robots, so this
particular surgery is also covered under this policy.
It covers some of the surgeries. There is a
limit given for this. You get up to ₹1 for the
middle surgery of the arrested party, that is, there is no
limit on that. But for medical shops
near you, there is first life, that is,
if you want to take a second opinion from a doctor, then
you are eligible under this policy.
Talking about emergency ambulance, then
hospitalization air ambulance
is covered up to ₹2000 in this policy. Talking about share decoration,
share decoration means
that you post like this and there
is no typing regarding room rent in it. There is no
typing of this kind, but the member
realizes that when you are going to the hospital
and if you take a room there, then
half of the overall sum insured
remains because you can use it for the remaining treatment. So,
here
some additional benefit for share decoration should be
given by the company. Now we talk about
some optional things in the policy.  There are benefits
that you can take if you want, and if
you don't want to, you can opt out. But
one of these benefits is the Saved Benefit, which
I personally like very much. And the Tablet
Benefit is that you must have noticed that during a hospital stay
or after a
hospital stay, there are
many non-par items like gloves, purse, etc.
which were
not available in any policy earlier. But here,
if you take this benefit or
turn off this optional benefit, then
you get all those benefits. There is a donation hospital
cash earthquake benefit.
You can understand its benefit in this way
or you can take it in this way.
Suppose someone
is admitted in a hospital and the relatives who come to visit you there, then
their
expenses, small expenses, those complex
gas can be covered by the benefits.
Now let's talk about personal accident cover,
you can also take additional coverage in this policy.
You can take this policy in
both individual and plot mode.
If you select the individual option, that is,
husband, wife and two children,
and if you leave the individual and individual option for all four, then
you get a discount of up to 10% on the premium.
Apart from this, if we talk about
our health care plan, the
company has given an additional premium discount for those who are medical practitioners.
Now, if we talk about some other benefits, then now the
company has
7600 more network hospitals
on the table. It is bringing a very good benefit here
because the company also
says here that it
gives assurance of cashless claim within just 30 minutes
and so the company gives one of the benefits,
this plan is called Point Opted SPO
C. This means that the company has some
selected hospitals and if you
go there, then you will get a lemon there.
Representatives are
available who help you completely in getting the policy i.e.
in filling your form or
completing other formalities.
Apart from this, if we talk about if you make
changes in this policy, then it is Life Long Dead
One, this means that if you have taken
entry in this policy in any match i.e. maximum entries payer up to 6558, then you
can continue this policy wherever you want. Second
benefits company also gives that if you have
taken the policy and you want to
advance your premium at the time of renewal, that is, you
want to increase the premium, then you can do that also in this policy.
Along with this, the
company also gives portability benefit here. The company
says that if your access link has a
policy running somewhere, then you
can transfer that policy to the vested interest here. There are some
more
benefits, if I may add, then please support if you
want to take a line policy and
they have any diabetes,
provided they are on insulin.  No, if there is some
type of diabetes, then
how would the company accept it with some loading, so
overall if I talk then it is a very good Chanak, a
very competitive product in the market and
today, keeping in mind the care needs, almost
all the features are available in this product
and if I talk then I have bought the
same product for myself and my family, so
finally if
you have some other queries
related to this product then please you
can coordinate with my team on the number written in the description and in the
near future we will keep bringing many such
products for you people on a very regular
basis, thank you, thank you so much